Guide to the Science fiction magazines, about 1946-2006.
Science fiction magazines
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Science fiction magazines, about 1946-2006.
8032
Charles E., Gribble
15 cubic feet.
Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 78 science fiction magazine titles.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 78 science fiction magazine titles, including complete or near complete runs of Analog, Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, Astounding, Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, and Galaxy.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Gribble, Charles E.,
Subjects:
Science fiction.; Science fiction, American.; Science fiction; Science fiction, American
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- 10 Story Fantasy, 1951 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 1: Spring
- Arkham Sampler, 1949 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 1: Winter
- Cosmic Stories, 1941 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 1: July
- Dynamic Science Fiction, 1953 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 4: Mar, Jun, Aug, Oct
- Dynamic Science Fiction, 1954 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 1: Jan
- Fantastic Story, 1952 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 2: Summer, Sep
- Fantastic Story, 1953 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 2: Jul, Sep
- Fantastic Story, 1954 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 3: Winter, Spring, Fall
- Future Science Fiction, 1953 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 1: Nov
- Future Science Fiction, 1954 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 2: Jan, Mar
- Out of this World Adventures, 1950 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 1: Dec
- Planet Stories, 1954 (Box 1)
  Notes: "Sound of Thunder" By Ray Bradbury
- Science Fiction, 1940 (Box 1)
  Number of Issues: 3: Mar, Jun, Oct
- Science Fiction, 1941 (Box 1)
- Science Fiction, 1941 (Box 2)
  Number of Issues: 2: Jun, Sep
- Science Fiction Quarterly, 1952 (Box 2)
  Number of Issues: 1: Feb
- Science Fiction Quarterly, 1953 (Box 2)
  Number of Issues: 2: Aug, Nov
- Science Fiction Quarterly, 1954 (Box 2)
  Number of Issues: 4: Feb, May, Aug, Nov
- Startling Stories, 1946 (Box 2)
  Number of Issues: 3: Spring, Fall, Winter
- Startling Stories, 1947 (Box 2)
  Number of Issues: 4: Jan, Mar, Jul, Nov
- Startling Stories, 1948 (Box 2)
  Number of Issues: 3: Jan, Jul, Sept
- Startling Stories, 1949 (Box 2)
  Number of Issues: 2: Mar, Jul
- Startling Stories, 1950 (Box 2)
- Startling Stories, 1950 (Box 3)
  Number of Issues: 4: May, Jul, Sep, Nov
- Startling Stories, 1951 (Box 3)
  Number of Issues: 6: Jan, Mar, May, Jul, Sep, Nov
- Startling Stories, 1953 (Box 3)
  Number of Issues: 2: Jan, Feb
- Startling Stories, 1953 (Box 3)
  Number of Issues: 5: Feb, Mar, Jun, Aug, Oct
- Startling Stories, 1954 (Box 3)
  Number of Issues: 4: Jan, Spring, Summer, Fall
- Startling Stories, 1955 (Box 3)
  Number of Issues: 1: Summer
- Stirring Science Stories, 1941 (Box 4)
  Number of Issues: 1: Jun
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1946 (Box 4)
  Number of Issues: 3: Summer, Fall, Winter
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1947 (Box 4)
  Number of Issues: 6: Feb, Apr, Jun, Aug, Oct, Dec
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1948 (Box 4)
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1949 (Box 4)
  Number of Issues: 4: Apr, Jun, Aug, Dec
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1950 (Box 4)
  Number of Issues: 4: Feb, Jun, Aug, Oct
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1951 (Box 5)
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1952 (Box 5)
  Number of Issues: 3: Feb, Apr, Jun
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1953 (Box 5)
  Number of Issues: 4: Feb, Apr, Jun, Aug, Nov
  Notes: 2 Copies of Feb and Apr
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1954 (Box 5)
  Number of Issues: 3: Spring, Summer, Winter
- Tops In Science Fiction, 1953 (Box 5)
- Treasury of Great Science Fiction Stories, 1965 (Box 5)
  Number of Issues: 1: No. 2
- Two Complete Science Adventure Books, 1953 (Box 5)
- Wonder Story Annual, 1952 (Box 5)
  Number of Issues: 1: Vol. 1 No. 3
- Wonder Story Annual, 1953 (Box 5)
  Number of Issues: 1: Vol. 2 No. 1
- Amazing Stories, 1953 (Box 6)
  Number of Issues: 4: Apr-May, Jun-Jul, Aug-Sep, Oct-Nov
- Amazing Stories, 1954 (Box 6)
  Number of Issues: 5: (Dec 1953-)Jan, Mar, May, Sep, Nov
- Amazing Stories, 1955 (Box 6)
  Number of Issues: 2: Jan-Nov
- Amazing Stories, 1958 (Box 6)
  Number of Issues: 2: Feb, Mar
- Amazing Science Fiction, 1976 (Box 6)
  Notes: Continues from Amazing Stories
- Amazing Science Fiction, 1977 (Box 6)
  Number of Issues: 3: Mar, Jul, Oct
- Amazing Science Fiction, 1978 (Box 6)
- Analog, 1960 (Box 6)
  Number of Issues: 5: Aug-Dec
  Notes: Cover title for Aug. and Sept. issues has words "Astounding" and "Analog" superimposed
- Analog, 1961 (Box 6)
  Number of Issues: 2: Jan-Feb
- Analog, 1961 (Box 7)
  Number of Issues: 10: Mar-Dec
- Analog, 1962 (Box 7)
  Number of Issues: 12: Jan-Dec
- Analog, 1963 (Box 7)
  Notes: Continues as large-format, Mar. 1963-Mar. 1965
- Analog, 1965 (Box 7)
  Number of Issues: 2: Apr-May
- Analog, 1965 (Box 8)
  Number of Issues: 6: Jun-Jul, Sep-Dec
- Analog, 1966 (Box 8)
- Analog, 1967 (Box 8)
  Number of Issues: 7: Jan-May, Jul-Aug
- Analog, 1967 (Box 9)
  Number of Issues: 4: Sep-Dec
  Notes: 2 copies of Nov. and Dec.
- Analog, 1968 (Box 9)
  Number of Issues: 11: Jan-Nov
- Analog, 1969 (Box 9)
  Number of Issues: 7: Jan-Jul
- Analog, 1969 (Box 10)
- Analog, 1970 (Box 10)
- Analog, 1971 (Box 10)
- Analog, 1971 (Box 11)
  Notes: 2 copies of Nov.
- Analog, 1972 (Box 11)
- Analog, 1973 (Box 11)
  Number of Issues: 6: Jan-Jun
- Analog, 1973 (Box 12)
  Number of Issues: 6: Jul-Dec
- Analog, 1974 (Box 12)
- Analog, 1975 (Box 12)
  Number of Issues: 5: Jan-May
- Analog, 1975 (Box 13)
  Number of Issues: 7: Jun-Dec
- Analog, 1976 (Box 13)
  Notes: Jan-April: Children of Dune by Frank Herbert
- Analog, 1977 (Box 13)
  Number of Issues: 6: Jan-June
  Notes: June: "The Screwfly Solution" by James Tiptree, Jr. (as Racoona Sheldon)
- Analog, 1977 (Box 14)
  Number of Issues: 6: July-Dec
  Notes: Aug.: "Ender'ss Game" by Orson Scott Card
- Analog, 1978 (Box 14)
- Analog, 1979 (Box 14)
- Analog, 1979 (Box 15)
- Analog, 1980 (Box 15)
  Notes: 2 copies of Apr.
- Analog, 1981 (Box 15)
  Number of Issues: 7: Jan-Jun
  Notes: 2 copies of Mar.
- Analog, 1981 (Box 16)
- Analog, 1982 (Box 16)
  Number of Issues: 13: Jan-Dec
  Notes: 2 copies of Mar. and Sept.; no April Issue published
- Analog, 1983 (Box 16)
- Analog, 1983 (Box 17)
  Number of Issues: 6: Aug-Dec
  Notes: 2 copies of Dec.
- Analog, 1984 (Box 17)
  Notes: 2 Issues published in December
- Analog, 1985 (Box 17)
  Number of Issues: 8: Jan-Aug
- Analog, 1985 (Box 18)
  Number of Issues: 5: Sep-Dec
  Notes: 2 Issues published in September
- Analog, 1986 (Box 18)
  Notes: 2 Issues published in December; Nov.: "Eifelheim" by Michael F. Flynn
- Analog, 1987 (Box 18)
  Number of Issues: 7: Jan-July
- Analog, 1987 (Box 19)
- Analog, 1988 (Box 19)
- Analog, 1989 (Box 19)
- Analog, 1990 (Box 20)
- Analog, 1991 (Box 20)
- Analog, 1991 (Box 21)
- Analog, 1992 (Box 21)
- Analog, 1993 (Box 21)
  Number of Issues: 9: Jan-Aug
- Analog, 1993 (Box 22)
- Analog, 1994 (Box 22)
  Notes: 2 Issues published in December; 2 copies of Nov.
- Analog, 1995 (Box 22)
  Number of Issues: 9: Jan-Sep
- Analog, 1996 (Box 23)
  Number of Issues: 4: Oct-Dec
  Notes: 2 Issues published in December; 2 copies of Mid-Dec.
- Analog, 1997 (Box 23)
  Number of Issues: 11: Jan-Dec
  Notes: Jul./Aug. double Issue
- Analog, 1998 (Box 23)
- Analog, 1999 (Box 24)
- Analog, 2000 (Box 24)
  Number of Issues: 9: Jan-Oct
- Analog, 2000 (Box 25)
  Number of Issues: 2: Nov-Dec
- Analog, 2001 (Box 25)
- Analog, 2002 (Box 25)
- Analog, 2003 (Box 25)
- Analog, 2003 (Box 26)
  Number of Issues: 9: Mar-Dec
- Analog, 2004 (Box 26)
  Number of Issues: 10: Jan-Dec
  Notes: Jan./Feb. and Jul./Aug. double Issues
- Analog, 2005 (Box 26)
  Number of Issues: 6: Mar-Sep
- Analog, 2005 (Box 27)
  Number of Issues: 3: Oct-Dec
- Analog, 2006 (Box 27)
  Number of Issues: 6: Jan-Aug
- Analog Anthology, 1982 (Box 27)
  Number of Issues: 2: No. 2, 3
  Notes: No. 2: Readers' Choice; No. 3: Children of the Future
- Analog Anthology, 1983 (Box 27)
  Number of Issues: 1: No. 4
  Notes: Analog's Lighter Side
- Asimov's Science Fiction, 1992 (Box 27)
  Number of Issues: 3: Nov-Dec
- Asimov's Science Fiction, 1993 (Box 27)
- Asimov's Science Fiction, 1993 (Box 28)
- Asimov's Science Fiction, 1994 (Box 28)
- Asimov's Science Fiction, 1995 (Box 28)
  Number of Issues: 8: Jan-Jul, Mid Dec.
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1946 (Box 29)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1947 (Box 29)
  Notes: Jul.: "With Folded Hands" by Jack Williamson
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1948 (Box 29)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1948 (Box 30)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1949 (Box 30)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1950 (Box 30)
  Number of Issues: 10: Jan-Oct
  Notes: May: "Dianetics" by L. Ron Hubbard; Oct: "The Analytical Mind" by L. Ron Hubbard
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1950 (Box 31)
  Notes: 2 Copies of Dec. Issue
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1951 (Box 31)
  Notes: 2 Copies of Jan, Feb, Mar, Apr
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1952 (Box 31)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1953 (Box 32)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1953 (Box 32)
  Notes: Apr.-Jul.: Mission of Gravity by Hal Clement
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1954 (Box 32)
  Notes: Aug.: "The Cold Equations" by Tom Godwin
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1955 (Box 33)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1956 (Box 33)
  Notes: 2 Copies of Mar.; Feb.-Apr.: Double Star by Robert Heinlein; Oct.-Dec.: The Naked Sun by Isaac Asimov
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1957 (Box 33)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1957 (Box 34)
  Number of Issues: 8: Mar, May-Aug, Oct-Dec
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1958 (Box 34)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1959 (Box 34)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1959 (Box 35)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1960 (Box 35)
  Notes: Feb.-Jul.: Cover title has the words "Astounding" and "Analog" superimposed. Jan.-Mar.: Deathworld by Harry Harrison
- Authentic Science fiction, 1951 (Box 35)
  Number of Issues: 2: No. 15, No. 16
- Authentic Science fiction, 1952 (Box 35)
  Number of Issues: 4: No. 15,16,27,28
- Avon Fantasy Reader, 1947 (Box 35)
  Number of Issues: 5: No. 1-5
- Avon Fantasy Reader, 1948 (Box 35)
  Number of Issues: 2: No. 6-7
- Avon Fantasy Reader, 1948 (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 1: No. 8
- Avon Fantasy Reader, 1949 (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 3: No. 9-11
- Avon Fantasy Reader, 1950 (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 3: No. 12-14
- Avon Fantasy Reader, 1951 (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 3: No. 15-17
- Avon Fantasy Reader, 1952 (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 1: No. 18
- Avon Science Fiction Reader, 1951 (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 2: No. 1-2
- Avon Science Fiction Reader, 1952 (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 1: No. 3
- Avon Science Fiction Reader, 1953 (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 1: Jan.
- Best Science Fiction from Worlds of If Magazine, [1964?] (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 1: No. 1
- Beyond Fantasy Fiction, 1953 (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 3: Jul, Sept, Nov
  Notes: 2 copies of Jul. and Sept.; "King of the Elves" by Philip K. Dick
- Beyond Fantasy Fiction, 1954 (Box 36)
  Number of Issues: 5: Jan, Mar, May, Jul, Sept
- Beyond Fiction, 1954 (Box 37)
  Number of Issues: 1: No. 9
  Notes: Continues from Beyond Fantasy Fiction
- Beyond Fiction, 1955 (Box 37)
  Number of Issues: 1: No. 10
- Cosmos Science Fiction and Fantasy, 1953 (Box 37)
  Notes: 2 copies of No. 1
- Dream World, 1953 (Box 37)
  Number of Issues: 1: Feb.
- Fantastic, 1952 (Box 37)
  Number of Issues: 1: Fall
- Fantastic, 1953 (Box 37)
  Number of Issues: 4: Jan-Feb, Jul, Aug, Sep-Oct, Nov-Dec
- Fantastic, 1954 (Box 37)
  Number of Issues: 5: Jan-Feb, Apr, Jun, Aug, Dec
- Fantastic, 1955 (Box 37)
  Number of Issues: 4: Feb, Apr, Jun, Aug
- Fantastic, 1956 (Box 37)
- Fantastic, 1958 (Box 37)
- Fantastic Stories, 1976 (Box 37)
  Number of Issues: 1: Aug
- Fantastic Universe, 1952 (Box 37)
  Number of Issues: 1: Jun-Jul
- Fantastic Universe, 1953 (Box 38)
  Number of Issues: 2: Aug-Sep, Oct-Nov
- Fantastic Universe, 1954 (Box 38)
  Number of Issues: 7: Jan, Mar, May, Jul, Sep, Oct, Nov
  Notes: 2 Copies of May; May: "Survey Team" by Philip K. Dick
- Fantastic Universe, 1955 (Box 38)
  Number of Issues: 6: Feb, Mar, Jun, Jul, Oct, Nov
- Fantastic Universe, 1956 (Box 38)
  Number of Issues: 3: Jan, Sep, Oct
  Notes: Jan.: "The Minority Report" by Philip K. Dick
- Fantastic Universe, 1957 (Box 38)
  Number of Issues: 1: May
- Fantastic Universe, 1958 (Box 38)
- Fantasy Magazine, 1953 (Box 38)
  Number of Issues: 3: Mar, Jun, Aug
- Fantasy Fiction, 1953 (Box 39)
  Notes: Continues from Fantasy Magazine
- Future Science Fiction, 1954 (Box 39)
  Number of Issues: 3: Jun, Aug, Oct
- Galaxy, 1950 (Box 39)
  Number of Issues: 2: Nov, Dec
- Galaxy, 1951 (Box 39)
  Number of Issues: 12: Jan - Dec
  Notes: Feb.: "The Fireman" by Ray Bradbury (expanded into Fahrenheit 451); Sept.-Nov.: The Puppet Masters by Robert Heinlein; 2 Copies of April and June
- Galaxy, 1952 (Box 39)
  Notes: Jan.-Mar.: The Demolished Man by Alfred Bester; Oct.: "Baby is Three" by Theodore Sturgeon (expanded into More Than Human)
- Galaxy, 1952 (Box 40)
  Number of Issues: 12: Sep-Dec
- Galaxy, 1953 (Box 40)
  Notes: Jan.: "The Defenders" by Philip K. Dick; Oct.-Dec.: Caves of Steel by Isaac Asimov
- Galaxy, 1954 (Box 40)
- Galaxy, 1954 (Box 41)
- Galaxy, 1955 (Box 41)
  Number of Issues: 9: Jan-Apr, Jun-Jul, Sep-Nov
- Galaxy, 1956 (Box 41)
  Notes: Oct.-(Jan. 1957): The Stars My Destination by Alfred Bester; 2 copies of Oct.
- Galaxy, 1957 (Box 42)
  Number of Issues: 11: Jan-Apr, Jun-Dec
- Galaxy, 1958 (Box 42)
  Notes: Aug.: "To Marry Medusa" by Theodore Sturgeon
- Galaxy, 1959 (Box 42)
- Galaxy, 1959 (Box 43)
  Number of Issues: 5: Apr, Jun, Aug, Oct, Dec
- Galaxy, 1960 (Box 43)
  Number of Issues: 5: Feb, Apr, Jun, Aug, Oct
- Galaxy, 1961 (Box 43)
  Number of Issues: 2: Aug, Oct
- Galaxy, 1962 (Box 43)
  Number of Issues: 5: Feb, Jun, Aug, Oct, Dec
- Galaxy, 1963 (Box 43)
  Number of Issues: 2: Feb, Aug
- Galaxy, 1963 (Box 44)
  Number of Issues: 1: Oct
- Galaxy, 1965 (Box 44)
  Number of Issues: 3: Feb, Oct, Dec
  Notes: Dec.: "'Repent, Harlequin!' Said the Ticktockman" by Harlan Ellison
- Galaxy, 1966 (Box 44)
- Galaxy, 1971 (Box 44)
- Galaxy, 1972 (Box 44)
- Galaxy, 1974 (Box 44)
- Galaxy, 1976 (Box 44)
  Number of Issues: 2: Sep, Dec
- Galaxy, 1977 (Box 44)
  Number of Issues: 8: Apr-Nov
- Galaxy, 1978 (Box 44)
  Number of Issues: 4: (Dec 1977-Jan) Feb-Apr
- Galaxy, 1978 (Box 45)
  Number of Issues: 3: Jun-Sep, Nov/Dec
- Galaxy, 1979 (Box 45)
  Number of Issues: 3: Mar-Apr, Jun-Jul, Sep-Oct
- Galaxy Science Fiction Novel, [1950-1953] (Box 45)
  Number of Issues: 16: No. 1 - 16
- Galaxy Science Fiction Novel, [1953-1954] (Box 46)
  Number of Issues: 4: No. 17-19, 22
- Great Science Fiction From Amazing, [1965] (Box 46)
- If, 1952 (Box 46)
  Number of Issues: 4: Mar, Jul, Sep, Nov
- If, 1953 (Box 46)
  Number of Issues: 6: Jan, March, May, July, Sep, Nov
  Notes: Sept: "A Case of Concience" by James Blish
- If, 1954 (Box 46)
  Number of Issues: 9: Jan, Mar-Oct
  Notes: 2 copies of Jun.
- If, 1954 (Box 47)
- If, 1955 (Box 47)
  Number of Issues: 3: Feb, Jun, Aug
- If, 1956 (Box 47)
  Number of Issues: 1: Apr
- If, 1958 (Box 47)
- If, 1963 (Box 47)
- If, 1966 (Box 47)
- If, 1971 (Box 47)
  Number of Issues: 2: Jan-Feb, Dec
- Imagination, 1950 (Box 47)
  Number of Issues: 2: Oct, Dec
- Imagination, 1951 (Box 47)
  Number of Issues: 5: Feb, Apr, Jun, Sep, Nov
- Imagination, 1952 (Box 47)
  Number of Issues: 7: Jan, Mar, May, Jul, Sep, Oct, Dec
- Imagination, 1953 (Box 48)
  Number of Issues: 11: Jan, Feb, Apr-Dec
- Imagination, 1954 (Box 48)
  Notes: 2 copies of Oct.
- Imagination, 1955 (Box 48)
  Number of Issues: 3: Jan-Mar
- Imagination, 1955 (Box 49)
  Number of Issues: 6: Apr-Jul, Oct, Dec
- Imaginative Tales, 1954 (Box 49)
  Number of Issues: 2: No. 1,2
- Imaginative Tales, 1955 (Box 49)
- Infinity, 1955 (Box 49)
- Infinity, 1956 (Box 49)
- Infinity, 1957 (Box 49)
  Number of Issues: 2: Feb, Jun
- Infinity, 1958 (Box 49)
  Number of Issues: 4: Jan, Apr, Jun, Aug
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1977 (Box 49)
  Number of Issues: 4: Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter
  Notes: 2 copies of Spring
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1978 (Box 49)
  Number of Issues: 4: Jan-Feb, Mar-Apr, May-Jun, Jul-Aug
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1978 (Box 50)
  Number of Issues: 2: Sep-Oct, Nov-Dec
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1979 (Box 50)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1980 (Box 50)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1980 (Box 51)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1981 (Box 51)
  Notes: 2 Issues published in Aug.
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1982 (Box 51)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1982 (Box 52)
  Number of Issues: 2: Dec
  Notes: 2 issues published in Dec.
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1983 (Box 52)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1984 (Box 52)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1985 (Box 53)
  Number of Issues: 12: Jan-Mid Dec
  Notes: First Dec issue missing
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1986 (Box 53)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1987 (Box 53)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1987 (Box 54)
  Number of Issues: 12: Feb-Dec
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1988 (Box 54)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1989 (Box 54)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1989 (Box 55)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1990 (Box 55)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1991 (Box 55)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1991 (Box 56)
  Number of Issues: 10: Apr-Dec
  Notes: 2 issues published in Dec.; 2 copies of Nov.
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction, 1992 (Box 56)
- Isaac Asimov's Science Fiction Anthology, 1979 (Box 56)
  Number of Issues: 1: Vol. 1
- Journal of Science Fiction, 1953 (Box 56)
  Number of Issues: 1: Vol. 1, No. 4
  Notes: Fanzine; Final Issue; Includes 1952 Magazine index
- Magazine of Fantasy, 1949 (Box 56)
  Notes: First Issue; continues as Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1950 (Box 56)
  Number of Issues: 2: Winter/Spring, Summer
  Notes: Continues from Magazine of Fantasy
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1950 (Box 57)
  Number of Issues: 2: Fall, Dec
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1951 (Box 57)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1952 (Box 57)
  Number of Issues: 3: Feb, Sep, Oct
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1953 (Box 57)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1954 (Box 57)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1954 (Box 58)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1955 (Box 58)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1956 (Box 58)
  Notes: Oct.-Dec.: The Door Into Summer by Robert Heinlein; 2 copies of Nov.
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1957 (Box 58)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1957 (Box 59)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1958 (Box 59)
  Number of Issues: 11: Jan-Oct, Dec
  Notes: Aug.-Oct.: Have Spacesuit, Will Travel by Robert Heinlein
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1959 (Box 59)
  Notes: Apr.: "Flowers for Algernon" by Daniel Keyes
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1959 (Box 60)
  Notes: Oct.-Nov.: Starship Soldier [Starship Troopers] by Robert Heinlein
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1960 (Box 60)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1961 (Box 60)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1961 (Box 61)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1962 (Box 61)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1963 (Box 61)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1963 (Box 62)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1964 (Box 62)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1965 (Box 62)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1965 (Box 63)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1966 (Box 63)
  Notes: Apr.: "We Can Remember it for You Wholesale" by Phillip K. Dick
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1967 (Box 63)
  Notes: Dec.: "The Cloud Sculptors of Coral D" by J.G Ballard
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1968 (Box 63)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1968 (Box 64)
  Number of Issues: 11: Feb-Dec
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1969 (Box 64)
  Notes: Oct.: "The Electric Ant" by Philip K. Dick
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1970 (Box 64)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1970 (Box 65)
  Number of Issues: 9: Apr-Dec
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1971 (Box 65)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1972 (Box 65)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1972 (Box 66)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1973 (Box 66)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1974 (Box 66)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1974 (Box 67)
  Notes: Dec.-(Jan. 1975): Venus on the Half Shell by Philip Jose Farmer (as Killgore Trout)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1975 (Box 67)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1976 (Box 67)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1976 (Box 68)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1977 (Box 68)
  Notes: 2 copies of Feb. and Mar.
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1977 (Box 69)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1978 (Box 69)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1979 (Box 69)
  Number of Issues: 3: Jan-Apr
  Notes: Feb.-Apr.: On Wings of Song by Thomas M. Disch
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1979 (Box 70)
  Number of Issues: 9: May-Dec
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1980 (Box 70)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1981 (Box 70)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1981 (Box 71)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1982 (Box 71)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1982 (Box 72)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1983 (Box 72)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1984 (Box 72)
  Notes: Jun.: "The Ballad of the Flexible Bullet" by Stephen King
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1984 (Box 73)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1985 (Box 73)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1986 (Box 73)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1986 (Box 74)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1987 (Box 74)
  Notes: 2 copies of May
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1988 (Box 74)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1988 (Box 75)
  Notes: 2 copies of Aug.
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1989 (Box 75)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1989 (Box 76)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1990 (Box 76)
  Notes: Apr.: "The Last Feast of Harlequin" by Thomas Ligotti
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1991 (Box 76)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1991 (Box 77)
  Number of Issues: 6: Jun-Dec
  Notes: Oct./Nov. double Issue
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1992 (Box 77)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1993 (Box 77)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1993 (Box 78)
  Number of Issues: 8: Apr-Dec
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1994 (Box 78)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1995 (Box 78)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1995 (Box 79)
  Number of Issues: 10: Feb-Dec
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1996 (Box 79)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1997 (Box 80)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1998 (Box 80)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1998 (Box 81)
  Number of Issues: 2: Oct/Nov, Dec
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1999 (Box 81)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 2000 (Box 81)
- Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 2000 (Box 82)
  Number of Issues: 4: Aug-Dec
- Most Thrilling Science Fiction Ever Told, [1966] (Box 82)
- Orbit Science Fiction, [1953] (Box 82)
- Other Worlds, 1951 (Box 82)
  Number of Issues: 1: Sep
- Other Worlds, 1952 (Box 82)
  Number of Issues: 6: Jan, Mar, Jun-Aug, Dec
- Other Worlds, 1953 (Box 82)
  Number of Issues: 4: Jan, Mar, Apr, Jul
- Satellite Science Fiction, 1957 (Box 82)
  Number of Issues: 2: Feb, Apr